

PERSONAL INFORMATION

- https://gading.dev
- nttps://github.com/sutanlab
- in /in/gading-nasution
- @ /gadingnst
- **** +6289665813871

SKILLS

Personal Skills

- Research
- Problem Solving
 - Team Work
 - Patient

Technical Skills

- GIT
- Javascript/Typescript
- React Web/Native
 - Next - Node
 - Express

Sutan Gading Fadhillah Nasution

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, FRONTEND

ABOUT

I'm **Software Engineer** who specialized in **frontend** side, but also have an ability to code in **backend** side. Very passionate about modern web and mobile technology using **JavaScript/TypeScript** while taking into consideration the latest trends and techniques. I wrote the code structure cleanly and optimally. And I would be a fast learner to doing a new things and build a good teamwork either.

I've also made several side and open-source project on **GitHub** for fun, and maybe be useful for people who have used it.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SIRCLO 2021 - Present

Software Engineer, ORAMI Core

- Became part of the SIRCLO group when Orami was acquired by SIRCLO
- Joined Core Team as a Core Frontend Developer on Orami
- Doing R&D about improving web performance and code scalability
- Doing R&D design guidelines with UI/UX Team.
- Creating some utilities for supporting another Squad to develop app services

ORAMI 2019 - 2021

Frontend Developer

Helping Orami to develop application services for simplifying parenting with technology throughout Southeast Asia.

PT. TEL Pulp & Paper Jul 2018 - Aug 2018

Internship Programmer

During internship, My internship team and me created a system and web application called the e-log tracking system. This application is useful for employees of PT. TEL to track log shipments from vendors to PT. TEL

EDUCATION

2016 - 2019

State of Polytechnic Sriwijaya, Palembang Diploma III of Computer Engineering Department

2013 - 2016

SMK Muhammadiyah 1, Palembang Computer & Network Engineering Department